

WEB DEVELOPER & PROJECT MANAGER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a web developer who is proficient in both back-end and front-end frameworks, with more than five years' experience.

From a young age I was curious to understand how a computer works. I felt intrigued about how pressing on a button would lead to an action. This idea led me to pursue Code Development in all schooling advancements.

My passion for coding is a reflexion of my inquisitive attitude, I am motivated to learn more on daily basis and I look for new challenges that allow me to achieve self growth together with professional improvement.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

International Experience for 4 months

As the world was locked down due to Covid 19, I was living in Bratislava, Slovakia, balancing remote work with cultural diversity. In Bratislava I was able to improve my language skills, to focus on personal growth and to balance professional assignments with foreign adventure.

Workshop Speaker

related with Gender and Workplace Equality. I have an interest in promoting LGBT awareness, and I have taken part on diverse opportunities, both during work occasions and private events.

Instructor

My experience includes coaching and lecturing clients on product specifics.

Courses

udemy - Building Cross Plataform Apps with Xamarin and C# - 2017

Microsoft - JavaScript for Experienced Developer -

CEFOLgest - Course Initial Teacher Training 2016

WORK HISTORY

Full-Stack Freelance Developer

Nov 2019 - present

Technology: Javascript, Nodejs, PHP, HTML, CSS, Postgres.

Full-Stack Developer & Project Manager

IdealMais Lda. , Braga | Otc 2019 - present

Technology: Javascript, Nodejs, PHP, HTML, CSS, Postgres.

Information Technology Consultant

Garagem São João do Souto, Braga / Jun 2019 - present Financing Software; Hardware; Riper Equipment;

Senior Web Developer

Skillmind - Consultoria e Sistemas de Informação, S.A., Braga / Jan 2016 to Nov 2019

Software Development: WebSig Software Technology: Java, HTML, CSS, Postgres, Openlayers

Junior Web Developer

Skillmind - Consultoria e Sistemas de Informação, S.A., Braga. / Nov 2014 to Dec 2015.

Software Development; WebSig Software Technology: Java, HTML, CSS, Postgres, Openlayers

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Master Degree Computing Science

University of Minho, Engineering School. / Sept 2017 -

Degree Computing Science

Superior Institute Miguel Torga, Coimbra. / Sept 2010 to Sept 2014

Technological Course on the field of Computer **Studies**

High School Avelar Brotero, Coimbra. /Sept 2004 to Jun 2009

KEY COMPETENCIES

Java; Javascript; JQUERY; CSS; REACT; NODE; VUEJS; HTML; Oracle; Bootstrap; PHP; Postgres; MYSQL; MongoDB; Illustrator; Project Management

LANGUAGES

PORTUGUES (NATIVE)

ENGLISH

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Hiking; Canoeing / Kayaking; going to the Gym; Music, Cinema, being with Friends and Family; Travelling

CONTACT DETAILS